Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep
within your dreams Taking aim
for your heart so it would
seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious, serious,
oh Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls filled between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in
United gently bringing up our thought
again, yeah We're the foolish ones we love,
we'll carry on
Till we see the light, the sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core is
against myself forevermore Come on,
let's do it now,
let's go The bonds built between us,
they will show So what we don't know,
that's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes,
we're the Super Bowers Super Bowers Yes,
we're the Super Bowers
What the hell are you bastards doing here?
Eat this!
We're not even leaving a scratch!
What the hell are they?
Sanji
This is nothing to do with you,
take your captain and escape!
We don't need you here thought
they could outsmart us.
We'll make them pay for that
Then it just so happens all the
enemy forces are gathered here
for us to destroy lucky us.
Is that your story?
Think about Jerma's iron skin is true.
This is crazy
I was told you were all dead.
How'd you survive our attack?
What do you mean?
Nastort, they had 10,000
soldiers with him.
Are you telling me that your
kingdom defeated them all?
Soldiers?
They were more like a
swarm of flies, really.
We swatted them all right
into the sea. You what?
Hey, this is Montdor.
Are you all right?
Nastort, please come in.
Basquiat, don't smoke! Anyone?
Someone pick up!
Answer me!
Scar Ball!
Ever since Pecum's betrayed us,
it has been one mauvaise
surprise after another today!
And why did Germans fleet up to
show up at home moments crucial?
What did you simpletons think we were
going to do with our technology anyway?
Stick to cake!
I will murder you.
Sanji, get moving already. Okay.
Germa is blasting the crap
out of Snack and his fleet.
Shouldn't we go help them?
Don't get distracted by their problems.
Our duty is to crush Straw Hat's ship.
Spread that message to
the fleet. Yes, ma 'am.
Montior dropped the ball.
He must have been outsmarted by Germa.
Lest you forget, you were outsmarted too.
I worked my ass off to
come here and help you.
Mama's hunger pains
are still going strong.
We're supposed to be safe here.
We traded part of ourselves to
live under an emperor's protection,
and then she just
destroys her own kingdom!
Um, it took Strewson days to make that
cake, and he's the best in the land.
We'll be long dead before we can throw
something together like that again.
Even Lady Pudding can't do it.
The cake has to be perfect, and
it has to be done right now.
A cake that'll make Big Mom lick her lips?
That's tricky. We're dead.
We'd better evacuate, I guess.
No way am I waiting around here.
We should bolt while we can.
Big Mom, where is she?
Fluffy Island.
Poor Lady Chiffon.
Mama's gonna pound that poor girl to bits.
I couldn't stop a rampage.
Mama's coming.
We're all due.
Lady Chiffon.
I heard they have a cake,
but why'd they bring it here?
Run away!
Quarter them already.
Hey, Jinbei.
What's going on with Jerma's fleet?
They're attacking the enemy, but do
you think they're here to save us?
That must be their
intention as it would have
been far more convenient
for them to escape Sure,
but if we let our guard down then they
might turn those cannons on us next.
Who knows what their plan might be?
You're right.
For example, maybe Rachel
came to show me a -
Hey, can you guys hear me?
Sanji, I'm afraid we can't get any
closer to the island than we are now.
Don't worry, just sail in the
direction of the harbor at full speed.
I'm heading there as we speak.
Hey, Sanji, is Luffy okay?
Yeah, I got him, but I
can't talk right now.
Just get the ship moving, please.
No problem.
Starboard, turn.
Let's do this.
Starboard, ho.
Come on, Sanji! Yay!
Uchi-ataka!
Fire on Germa!
Where did Blackleg go?
I can't see a damn thing!
There he is!
Shoot him!
Hum him down!
That's right.
Don't let him get away,
no matter the cost.
Straw Hat Luffy can never be
forgiven for what he's done.
The truth is, he didn't trick
Katakuri and run away to hide.
Instead, he faced him head on.
What do you mean, Barrel?
Wanna know what really happened
in the mirror world, huh?
Cause I'll tell you.
The strongest fighter in the world,
the man who never faces
defeat and never lies down.
Our perfect beautiful brother.
He fought that door with Straw Hat.
And he lost!
It can't be.
Katakuri,
your flawless record
was broken by that runt.
It's a lie!
Our brother would never lose!
Straw Hat must have cheated!
There's no other way!
Little bastard!
We'll make him pay!
Then never speak of this again!
After him!
Shoot him dead.
Slice him to shreds!
Bound his face in!
Grind his bones to dust!
This is the end, Strawhart!
Time to die! Try!
Taste my fire.
Roast him alive, Oven!
Not so fast!
Spartan!
Sultry!
Ichichi?
Sanji, go!
You okay, Oven?
Can you stand?
This is getting old, Blackleg!
Hand him over!
I'll Smash you as many times as it takes!
It's...
guillotine!
Aaaaaah!
Oh, no!
No!
Aaaaaah!
Yonji?
You're clear! Here!
Now go!
I don't want to look at
you anymore, you lame ass.
Shoot him down!
We got this!
This one's for General Tazakuri!
I hate to break it to you,
but you're still too slow.
Me, Gene.
Get back here!
Let's go!
Strike!
Lightspeed sword!
Henry... Laser!
Oven, sir!
We're too late!
Those two are about to make
it to the coast! Already?
But how?
Bye, loser.
Have a nice flight.
Come in, snack.
Jack, Brownie, Joconda, shoot
those bastards down at the coast!
The head in your way!
Hey!
Was that somebody calling us just now?
Almost there. We got this!
Looks like they're moving into range.
Prepare to fire the tear gas.
One taste of this and
it'll sink like a rock!
Hey, buddy! What gives?
Say something! Hey! Hey!
It's Samma!
You won't lay a finger
on my little brother.
Not on my watch.
If I can just run away somehow
while we're in the east blue.
Then I'll be free, right?
I can live the rest of my life
without ever seeing Dad's face again.
Pink Hornet!
It's Straw Hat! Fire!
You're really high
maintenance, aren't you?
Better not let him go, alright?
Come on, Sanji!
Stop crying like a little baby!
Look, you can never come
back here, understand?
Run away!
And don't look back!
Sanji, you're the kindest
person I've ever met.
Don't ever change.
Stay safe!
You too!
All members of the fleet, target
Straw Hat is escaped from the island!
Sanji!
Hurry!
He made it!
I see him! Guys!
Sonji's coming and he's got Luffy too!
He's as reliable as they come! Luffy!
There it is, Luffy.
It's the Sonny!
Is dinner ready yet?
Hey, Press! Please respond!
How is Mama doing?
Veggie? The cake?
I'm freaking out here!
Kaku Island is a mess! It's crazy!
And this is about to get even worse!
You think I don't know that?
I'm lickety-looking at Mama
and Buggy at this very moment.
Press, are you okay?
Hey, it's Bavoie here.
Sorry, brother.
Press lost an arm and didn't
have it treated properly,
so he's kind of running
out of juice at the moment.
He what?
That's not lickety-relevant, all right?
Give me the snail.
We are waiting at sea.
Right outside.
Fluffy Island.
It's chaos.
Now we wait for her to eat it.
Dempster breaks, old pal.
Sorry it had to end like this.
You're a damn fine ship.
Saved our tail so many times.
Thanks, Nostra Costello.
And so long.
So one of three things could
happen next, let me explain:
one the cake is poisoned,
mama eats it and she dies;
two the poison doesn't affect
mama but the cake tastes bad.
In that case,
you'll still be Lickety longing for
cake and her rampage will continue.
And three,
the poison in the cake doesn't affect
her and miraculously it tastes good.
That's the only scenario
where we Lickety live.
Prepare yourselves.
Lickety like it or not, our fate
rests entirely on that wedding cake.
C 'est une catastrophe.
The whole country knows by now it's bad.
She's still out of control.
Did you hear nuts island
got wrecked pretty bad?
There's not gonna be
anything left of total land
with this like your team
and the cake is the blade.
Wait a second, where did
morgan's and Sexy go?
They left the island a little while back.
What are you kidding?
They'll tell the whole
world about this disaster.
Capture them before they get too far.
Yes sir, damn it that's
the last thing we need.
Our failures on the front
page of the newspaper.
That bird wouldn't pass
up on such a huge scoop!
This island is cursed!
Run for your lives!
We're gonna end up as a trash
heap, just like Nuts Island!
Lady Chabon betrayed us!
We can't count on her
or that traitor Veggie!
You're gonna get yourself
killed, sweetheart.
No.
Everything is going to be just fine.
I believe in the cake that Blackleg baked.
I don't know who trained him, but his
cooking is the finest I've ever witnessed.
Mama's hunger pangs will stop here.
There's no question in my mind.
Vito, Kaido, go nab a
ship and blow this joint.
Me and Shifan will catch up to you
once this little matter is settled.
Sure, you got it.
Stay safe.
We paid off our debt to the Straw Hats.
It did cost us... our ship.
They better survive this.
I didn't put my ass on the
line just for them to fail.
Mamma mamma.
My dear.
Uh...
Heck yeah!
We did it!
Bloopy!
City! Bloopy!
I was so worried! My door! Our floor!
Poor thing, you're all worn out.
Splendid work, the both of you!
Captain's in suspense, huh? Carrot...
Jeez, you're late.
What took you so long? Shut up!
So, did you knock out Katakuri?
Yeah.
It's so proud that you're my captain!
He fell asleep? No surprise.
Guys, those wounds are fresh.
Quick, Chopper, he's bleeding.
Hurry, you need to do some
doctoring on the double.
Right.
Sanji, you too, you got shot.
This, it's nothing, don't you worry.
Treat Luffy first.
All right, we're almost there.
They caught up!
We got too distracted!
Well, we'll just have to keep moving.
Treat him while we sail away!
Fire!
What now? No!
Chairman's backing them
up! Damn it! You're next!
Should we return fire?
No need for that.
We're fighting at the coast as well.
They can't do much.
Open fire on Straw Hat! Roger!
You really think Sanji's worth all this?
Are you a fool, Straw Hat?
You courted death coming
into an Emperor's territory.
victory was never possible
only retreat what could this
failure possibly offer you in
return he's useless just a failed
experiment his skin is soft
he bleeds when he's struck
despite his royal status he's
content to work as a lowly chef
his heart is easily swayed
he sacrifices himself
for the weak even if he
destroys himself in the
Well, see ya!
Thanks for all the help!
I ask you a question, Straw Hat!
Answer me!
Your dad's weird,
but he sure had a lot of nice stuff
to say about you all of a sudden.
What do you mean—you thought
he was complimenting me?
You're such a delight, always.
Finally—they
noticed that's a buttload of
ships—damn it, they cut us off.
They must have
circled from the other side of the island.
There's no escape—no,
we're already in their range—no way.
You're too slow—drop your card
and pay the price, you fool—no
carrot, never mind the fleet!
fool no carrot never mind the fleet I'll
cut you down on the spot. Did you wind?
Speed!
Greg?
Suchy!
That was huge!
We finally got close enough
for my power to reach them.
This should be fun.
Like playing the bowling hunt.
Not that I blame you.
How did they all get here so fast?
I wondered myself, but look closely.
They're all paddle ships!
That's cheating!
So what should we do?
This might be the end!
Our victory!
Snatched away at the last moment!
Keep up the assault!
Why is the sea lifting up?
You better leave the boss
alone, you bunch of jerks!
Or you're gonna pay!
What?
Wasn't he from Hoardy's crew?
What's he doing here?
Waratsumi!
Whoa!
Can't be!
Jibbe!
You saved us!
We came to say goodbye, Captain Sham!
Oh, or a former captain, we mean.
But we'll guide you to
safety just once more, okay?
You know, for old times' sake.
How can I say no?
Yeah!
Oh, wow!
What the hell?
He's gonna leak!
You don't think someone's
attacking us from below, do you?
I see fishmen down there!
Sneaky bastards, that's not fair!
Come up here and fight for real, damn you!
Let's go! You're dead!
Bastards!
Let the Straw Hats escape!
Ocean current!
Shoulder throw!
Hey, look!
They opened a path for us.
We'll hold them back for you,
don't worry—you won't lay a finger
on their ship, not on my watch.
Thank
you all, why didn't I notice sooner?
They disabled the territory slugs too.
too We'd all be dead without their help.
And here they've come to save me again.
Wow, Jinbe, your friends
sure are great, huh? Indeed.
See you guys!
Thanks a bunch!
Take care of Jinbe for us, Straw Hat.
And good luck!
Okay.
Fire!
It won't be that easy!
Now merge!
Oven, sir!
Don't you need to stay on Cacao Island?
We have a plan.
Barrel will take care of Jeremiah.
Nothing can withstand these
heavy metal composite rounds.
Not even Jerma's precious raid suits.
Go teach those pesky rats a
lesson for me! Yes, ma 'am!
That oven guy is back!
I will avenge Katakuri if
it's the last thing I do!
You'll never get out alive!
What happens next?
Have faith, everyone.
It'll be all right.
The man who baked that
cake is a chef among chefs.
Blackleg, wait!
It'll take all night
if you do it that way.
We can't cut corners.
There's no time.
I'll do it in two hours.
Are you kidding?
What are you grinning about?
This is a life-or-death situation.
Your entire crew could die!
Even more than that, this whole
country could get wiped out!
Sorry.
Just thinking of Big
Mom and how happy she's
gonna be when she finally gets her cake.
Who cares if she's happy?
She's trying to kill ya!
Mama!
Looks like the poison knocked her out.
This day is so lovely.
I could die.
It's so sweet and fluffy.
Finally!
My wedding cake!
She likes it.
She's okay?
I'm sure those bastards poisoned it.
But Mama's too powerful!
We shall sell them!
You did it!
I wish you could see how
happy she is, Blackleg.
How sweet, this treat, a fabulous feat.
So nostalgic, oh, where
is it from? Who cares?
It's yummy!
To all citizens of Tootoland.
Mama's rampage has ended at lickety last.
Thanks to the work of Mama's
thirty-fifth daughter putting herself,
Mama's hunger banks have been
satiated! Thank goodness.
We're very close to Kaku Island, so
I was certain we'd be next. Daddy!
Oh, we're safe now, little buddy!
I told you, didn't I?
Pudding to capture that
traitor she fought.
She knew exactly what she needed to bake.
The perfect cake for Mama.
Thank you, Lady Pudding.
She's a hero.
No doubt about it.
We love you, Lady Pudding. No.
It wasn't me.
Best catch!
Now
the
finish!
Marking...
Fiction!
Tropical torment!
Hurry!
Dive deeper down before you boil!
It's too hot, you guys!
I'm sorry!
That takes care of your
backup, doesn't it?
Nowhere left to run.
Not good. Oh, babe! Help!
Let's go straight ahead.
Yes, we got this now!
Snatch it!
Snatch it, Snatch it, Go.
Snatch it, madge it, Go.
Delish, delicious.
And it's all for me.
A flavor like none other that
the world has never seen.
The sort of splendid sweetness you
might taste in a dream. Let's see.
Oh, let's see.
Why could it be a flavor that's so mighty?
It brings back your dead puppy.
Orchiddy.
Fluffy as can be,
sweet as can be,
just a touch,
risky,
goodness,
oh my, look at the lights.
In the sky.
Anchoring fires.
And shimmering sparks.
A rainbow of shrapnel.
And a stroll in the park.
A ceremony.
Sergeant Tommy.
Hey.
Mother, would you like a bite?
A flavor that's covered in light.
I feel it in my soul shining bright.
Of course, it's just like that day.
The flavor of joy, you might say.
Happy birthday, Lin-Lin, eat up.
Maybe someday, not so far away.
Let's eat together, okay.
Laugh this and be, sweet as can be.
And just a touch.
Risky.
Hey, Martha, can I pull this off?
My dream, I mean.
Everyone is happy here.
Peaceful days without a fear.
Every race is welcome too.
Let your dreams come true.
But if you try to leave,
I'll run you right through.
Feel free to sign your soul away.
The prize for a peaceful day.
Here we're all a family.
But don't defy her majesty!
BIT MORE!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma!
It was just delish!
What a great meal!